Can you go a little longer?
もうちょい行ける?
Do this yourself...
自分でこの...
Also, please pass...
また、下通して...
Try spreading Monko out.
モン子広げてみ
hand...
て...
Can you see what it looks like?
どんなか見える?
You're so small, Monko.
ちっちゃいな、モン子
...
Something like that...
なんか ね、下の方に...
Delicious honey...
美味しい蜜が...
Come down a bit
ちょっと下降りて
...
girl can sit
女 の子座りできる
...
I'd like you to lick me.
ペ ロペロしてもらっていいんですけど
...
touch it with your right hand
右 手で触って
...
Shall I come in now?
もう ちょい入る?
In your mouth...
口の中...
Oh?
おえ?
I think...
ってなると思う...
It's only in this area...it's only up to this area.
この辺しか...この辺までしか入ってないから
...
using pero
ペ ロを使って
...
Can you lick the back?
裏 とか舐めれる?
At Pero
ペロで
...
lick it
ペ ロペロして
hey...
ね...
Feels good
気持ちいい
...
Can you make it slimy for a day?
一 日、ぬるぬるにできる?
slimy...
ぬるぬる...
The rod will also be full.
竿の方もいっぱいになる
...
Do you know how hard it got for a day?
一 日、固くなったの分かる?
Feels good
気持ちいい
...
Can I sleep?
寝 ていい?
Can I have you sleep?
寝てもらっていい?
Mouth, just a little...
口、ちょいで...
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Just put it in like this...
このまま入れて...
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Show me your cute face...here
可愛い顔見せて...こっち
...
Doesn't it hurt?
痛 くない?
Look at me a lot
いっぱいこっち見て
...
Here, here
こ っちね、ここね
...
tortoise
カ メ
Can you see it?
ラ 見れる?
Will you be on top?
上になってくれる?
It feels good to lick it...
ペロペロして気持ちいい...
wake up one day
一日、起きる
...
Are you just looking at it all day long?
一 日、ぐりぐり見てるのかね
...
He says his hips move really well.
め っちゃ腰の動きがいいって
...
Just behind
その まま後ろ
...
A very absorbing day...
め っちゃ吸い込まれる、一日...
Are you putting in effort now?
今、力入れてる?
Haven't you put it in?
入れてないの?
I won't leave you, now...
離れないね、これで...
Can you see it inside?
入ってるとこ見える?
Wrap this butt...
こっちのお尻巻いて...